jobs.af 2019-04-10

# Jobs in Afghanistan - Our policy

## NETLINKS PRIVACY AND COOKIE POLICY

Revised: 14 April, 2018

These days, we all need to be smart about the way we use our own personal data. Your privacy is taken very seriously at Jobs.af. Jobs.af strives to provide the safest possible environment for you to search and apply to jobs. Jobs.af Precautions. 

### Overview:

We have created this Privacy Policy to demonstrate our commitment to protecting information you submit. This Privacy Policy only applies to data gathered on the Jobs.af web site (the "Site"), and does not apply to any other information or web site. Please review this Privacy Policy periodically as we may update it from time to time. This Privacy Policy is effective as of January 1, 2010. Each time you visit the Site or provide us with information, you are, by doing so, accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy at that time. You agree that by using the Site you are expressly and affirmatively consenting to our use and disclosure of the information that you provide, and consenting to receive emails, as described below in this Privacy Policy. 

### Personal Information:

In order to operate the Site in an efficient and effective manner and provide users with information on job postings and services that may be of interest to them, Jobs.af may collect personal information, including contact information (such as an email address), from its users. In addition, this information allows us to provide users with private and secure areas to post and modify their original content on our site (e.g., jobs and resumes). We also automatically track certain information based upon your behavior on the Site and use this information to do internal research on our users' demographics, interests, and behavior to better understand, protect and serve users in general. This information may include the URL that a user has just come from (whether this URL is on our Site or not), the URL a user goes to next (whether this URL is on our Site or not), a user's computer browser information, and their IP address. You agree that Jobs.af may use your personal information to contact you and deliver information to you that, in some cases, is targeted to your interests (such as relevant job postings and services), or provides administrative notices or communications applicable to your use of the Site. By accepting this Privacy Policy, you expressly agree to receive this information. All users should be aware, however, that when they voluntarily display or distribute personal information (such as their email address or resume), that information can be collected and used by others. This may result in unsolicited messages from third parties for which Jobs.af is not responsible. Jobs.af may also disclose specific user information when we determine that such disclosure is necessary to comply with the law, to cooperate with or seek assistance from law enforcement or to protect the interests or safety of Jobs.af or other users of the Site. In addition, personal information we have collected may be passed on to a third party in the event of a transfer of ownership or assets or a bankruptcy of Jobs.af 

### About Cookies:

At Jobs.af, we use cookies only for the protection and convenience of our users. Cookies enable us to serve secure pages to our users without asking them to sign in repeatedly. If a user's system is idle for certain period of time, however, the cookie will expire, forcing the user to sign in again to continue their session. This prevents unauthorized access to the user's information while they are away from their computer. You may have the ability to reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent; however, some Jobs.af features or services may not function properly without cookies. Third-Party Cookies: We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit the Site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. 

### Advertising:

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information about you and your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services of interest to you. 

### What You Should Know:

Jobs.af cannot ensure that all of your private communications and other personal information will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Privacy Policy. Therefore, although we are committed to protecting your privacy, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personal information or private communications will always remain private. As a user of the Site, you understand and agree that you assume all responsibility and risk for your use of the Site, the internet generally, and the documents you post or access and for your conduct on and off the Site. 

### Protect Yourself:

  * Some Important Tips To Use When Dealing With Prospective Employers.
  * Never provide credit card or bank numbers or monetary transaction of any sort.
  * Be cautious when dealing with contacts outside of Afghanistan.
  * Do not provide any non-work related personal information (i.e. bank account details, credit card number, marital status, etc.) over the phone or online.

### Other Privacy Features On Jobs.af:

You never need to provide data to search for jobs. Logging into Jobs.af is always an optional task for you to take. 

### Post a Resume:

Posting your resume on Jobs.af puts you in front of hundreds of employers with open positions each day. When you post your resume, we automatically create a registration for you using the email address and password that you supply. When you return to the site in the future you will use that same email address and password to access and edit your existing resume. 

**Mobile Device ID.** If you access or use the NETLINKS Website on your mobile telephone or other mobile device, including tablets, we collect mobile device identifiers and IP Address. We may create and assign to your device an identifier that is similar to an account number. We may collect the device type and any other information you choose to provide, such as user name, geolocation or email address. 

**Mobile Analytics.** We use mobile analytics software to allow us to better understand the functionality of our mobile software on your phone. This software may record information such as how often you use the application, the events that occur within the application, aggregated usage, performance data, and where the application was downloaded from. We do not link the information we store within the analytics software to any personally identifiable information you submit within the mobile application. 

**Location Data.** If you access the NETLINKS Website using a mobile device, we may collect your physical location if you have enabled this feature. Even if you are not using a mobile device, information about your general location may be discernable from your device's IP address or the URLs we receive.
